## Pitphilai Kumar Pandey (1) Featured



Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Project Management, Program Management, Requirement Analysis, Agile Development, C, C++, Linux Shell Scripting, Data Structure, Algorithm, Git, CVS, Valgrind, Multithreading



Current Designation: Software Engineer -IT Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: Ciena Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Gurgaon Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, Gurgaon Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Project Management, Program Management, Requirement Analysis, Agile Development, C, C++, Linux Shell Scripting, Data

Structure, Algorithm, Git, CVS, Valgrind, Multithreading

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

## Summary

Software Engineer with 4+ years of work exposure in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Gap Analysis, Solution Architecture, Performance Tuning, Valgrind, GDB, C, C++, Linux, Debugger, data structure

# Work Experience

Ciena as Software Engineer -IT Mar 2020 to Till Date

Technologies and Environment C and Linux

Roles

Involve in debugging issues

Altran as Software Engineer May 2018 to Mar 2020

Technologies and Environment C++, C and Multithreading (Windows and VxWorks env)

Roles

Involve in design, features development and debugging issues

**Projects** 

QOS (quality of service): Implement QOS at application layer

User account Management for SNMPv3: To manage user account in SNMPv3 using encypted file. SSH interface Management: Enable/Disable ssh server according configuration file provided by users

## Cavisson Systems Pvt Ltd as Software Engineer

Jul 2015 to May 2018

Technologies and Environment C and Multithreading (Linux env)

#### Roles

Gather requirements, prepare design and coding

Involve in implementation of LPS (Log Parser System): It is a multithreaded daemon process which listen on specific port and start new thread on receiving request to start monitor.

Outbound Connections: A Mechanism to communicate with servers which exist of a cloud environment, where incoming connections are not allow.

Maintaining products stability: This is one of the major tasks which everyone needs to take care of existing functionality

## **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Information Technology) from Dr KN Modi Institute of Engineering and Technology, Modinagar in 2015

PG: in 0

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Linux, Windows		0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Gdb debugger, valgrind, visual studio		
C, Shell Scripting, C++		
GIT, CVS		
Data structure, Algorithm		

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			
Thai	Proficient			

#### **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

**Employment Status: Full time**